Welcome to Amazon.
Whether you're a seasoned seller or just getting started, Amazon can help you take your business
to the next level, putting your products in front of millions of shoppers worldwide.
You'll get access to time and money-saving programs like Fulfillment by Amazon, which can help you
scale your business quickly and reach global customers.
Brand owners can take advantage of Amazon Brand Registry, a free program that provides your brand
with additional benefits and protections.
Plus, take advantage of Amazon tools to help you advertise, boost sales, and discover new ways to
grow.
The first step to becoming an Amazon Seller is completing registration and setting up your selling
account.
To do this, you'll need to submit documents related to your identity and business if you have one,
and wait for Amazon to verify them.
We recommend reviewing our dedicated Amazon onboarding course
for more information, which is available during your registration process in the Selling Basics
tab.
While you wait for your account to be verified, there are a few steps you can take to set yourself
up for success.
In order to list products on Amazon, you'll likely need a unique product ID or GTIN,
and you can use this time to locate or obtain them.
If you're the owner of an eligible brand, you should also consider enrolling it in brand registry
while you wait.
Once you've completed registration and your verification has been processed, you'll be able to sign
into your selling account
where you will manage most of your day-to-day business when selling with Amazon.
If you have questions at any time, simply ask Seller Assistant, our AI chatbot, or explore Seller
University for additional guidance.
Once again, welcome  to Amazon.
We're so excited to be a part of your selling journey.